truthstar.com 2018-10-01

# Privacy Policy - Truthstar

### Privacy Policy

Truthstar is committed to the privacy of data and personal information that users enter in our website and give us. Kindly go through the privacy policy so that you know well the way truthstar uses the information entered by the readers.

  *  **1.** We guarantee that your personal information and birth details shall remain confidential. We will make our predictions as per the legal guidelines and regulations.
  *  **2.** We will not use your personal data for anything except for providing you astrological predictions.
  *  **3.** You have full rights and permission to view your profile and make changes in it whenever you want.
  *  **4.** Truthstar doesn’t sell and rent the user’s personal data

Since new services are added at certain time intervals, you should check this on our website. The privacy policy changes shall be given in this section. When you use truthstar, it is understood that you accept our privacy policy.

### 1-Type Of Personal Data We Collect From Users

 **a- Registration Data**  
We take users name, gender, email id, and birth details when you register on our website. We make our horoscopes with this information. The email id and its password provide security to the user profile. We cannot make your personal horoscopes if you don’t give us this information. Users are not required to provide any other personal data to us.  
**B-Log Files, IP Address And Cookies**  
Truthstar and third parties associated with it collect data about user’s actions. We do this to get impersonal demographic information. We use and note down the IP address of your computer for detecting problems that occur in the software and server used by us. The IP address is tracked so that we know about the demography and get information on the places from which our website is used by the readers. It helps us in administering our website and troubleshooting the problems that occur in it. It improves the performance of our website.  
**C-Order Forms**  
Order forms are used to collect your data for paid services and it remains confidential as per legal guidelines. We provide a guarantee that user’s personal data and information will not be used in any way by us.  
**D-Other Information**  
The information you give us by sending an email to us will not be displayed on your profile and it is meant only for solving the problems and issues for which you have sent the email to us.

### 2-Security

Truthstar does not store any payment information and data. The processing of the payment is highly secure. Your payment data is safe from unauthorized access. Industry standards for making an online payment and technical measures are used for processing payment on our website. However, we cannot give a guarantee for any possible risks in making an online payment.

### 3-Other Websites

Truthstar does contain links to a few other web pages and websites. We don’t take responsibility and neither do we give a guarantee on the privacy policy of the linked webpage on Truthstar.

### 4-Contacting Us

Users who have queries and doubts about this privacy policy and any other aspect of truthstar can get their queries answered by contacting us in our email address **customercare@truthstar.com**
